// lyrics for questions

let questions = [
  {
    question:
      "How is it in London? \nWhere were you while I'm wondering if I'll ever see you again?",
    choice1: "Lover",
    choice2: "Red (Taylor's Version)",
    choice3: "Fearless (Taylor's Version)",
    choice4: "1989",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How's one to know I'd live and die for moments that we stole on begged and borrowed time?",
    choice1: "Evermore",
    choice2: "Reputation",
    choice3: "Folklore",
    choice4: "Speak Now",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "I once believed love would be burning red but it's golden",
    choice1: "Folklore",
    choice2: "Red (Taylor's Version)",
    choice3: "1989",
    choice4: "Lover",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "This is me praying that this was the very first page not where the storyline ends",
    choice1: "Evermore",
    choice2: "Fearless (Taylor's Version)",
    choice3: "Speak Now",
    choice4: "Folklore",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Could've loved you all my life if you hadn't lеft me waiting in the cold",
    choice1: "Fearless (Taylor's Version)",
    choice2: "1989",
    choice3: "Evermore",
    choice4: "Red (Taylor's Version)",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "They are the hunters, we are the foxes\n and we run",
    choice1: "Reputation",
    choice2: "Folklore",
    choice3: "1989",
    choice4: "Fearless (Taylor's Version)",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Is this the end of all the endings? My broken bones are mending",
    choice1: "Reputation",
    choice2: "Folklore",
    choice3: "Lover",
    choice4: "Speak Now",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "I see you everywhere, the only thing we share is this small town",
    choice1: "Speak Now",
    choice2: "Lover",
    choice3: "Evermore",
    choice4: "Fearless (Taylor's Version",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Something wrapped all of my past mistakes in barbed wire",
    choice1: "Evermore",
    choice2: "Red (Taylor's Version)",
    choice3: "Reputation",
    choice4: "Folklore",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "The rumors are terrible and cruel but honey most of them are true",
    choice1: "Reputation",
    choice2: "1989",
    choice3: "Red (Taylor's Version)",
    choice4: "Fearless (Taylor's Version)",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Another name goes up in lights. You wonder if you’ll make it out alive",
    choice1: "1989",
    choice2: "Speak Now",
    choice3: "Red (Taylor's Version)",
    choice4: "Reputation",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "I made you my temple, my mural, my sky. Now I'm begging for footnotes in the story of your life",
    choice1: "Evermore",
    choice2: "Fearless (Taylor's Version)",
    choice3: "Reputation",
    choice4: "Red (Taylor's Version)",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "And you were wild and crazy, just so frustrating, intoxicating, complicated",
    choice1: "1989",
    choice2: "Lover",
    choice3: "Fearless (Taylor's Version)",
    choice4: "Red (Taylor's Version)",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "So I'll watch your life in pictures like I used to watch you sleep",
    choice1: "Evermore",
    choice2: "Speak Now",
    choice3: "Reputation",
    choice4: "Red (Taylor's Version)",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "And baby for you I would fall from grace just to touch your face",
    choice1: "Folklore",
    choice2: "Fearless (Taylor's Version)",
    choice3: "Lover",
    choice4: "Reputation",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Back when I was living for the hope of it all",
    choice1: "Red (Taylor's Version)",
    choice2: "Folklore",
    choice3: "1989",
    choice4: "Lover",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Stood there and watched you walk away from everything we had",
    choice1: "Speak Now",
    choice2: "Reputation",
    choice3: "Evermore",
    choice4: "1989",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "When you're young, you just run but you come back to what you need",
    choice1: "Speak Now",
    choice2: "Lover",
    choice3: "1989",
    choice4: "Folklore",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "And I broke down crying, was she worth this mess? After everything and that little black dress",
    choice1: "Fearless (Taylor's Version)",
    choice2: "Folklore",
    choice3: "1989",
    choice4: "Red (Taylor's Version)",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "And the ladies lunching have their stories about when you passed through town",
    choice1: "Folklore",
    choice2: "Red (Taylor's Version)",
    choice3: "Evermore",
    choice4: "Speak Now",
    answer: 3,
  },
];
